Council on Foreign Relations Records: Studies Department Series, 1918-2004: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Subseries 3C: Staffing, 1925-2004; 32.32 linear feet 78 boxes
  - Diebold, William, 1925-2000; 50 boxes (1 partial)
    - Correspondence, 1935-2000; 21 boxes
      - Miscellaneous, 1935-2000; 4 boxes (1 partial)
        - 1970, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 7)
        - 1971, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 8)
        - 1972, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 9)
        - 1973, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 10)
        - 1974, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 11)
        - 1975, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 12)
        - 1976, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 13)
        - 1977, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 14)
        - 1978, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 15)
        - 1979, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 16)
        - 1980, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 17)
        - 1981, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 18)
        - 1982, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 19)
        - 1983, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 1)
        - 1984, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 2)
        - 1985, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 3)
        - 1986, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 4)
        - 1987, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 5)
        - 1988, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 6)
        - 1989, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 7)
        - 1990, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 8)
        - 1991, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 9)
        - 1992, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 10)
        - 1993, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 11)
        - 1994, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 12)
        - 1995, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 13)
        - 1996, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 14)
        - 1999, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 15)
        - 2000, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 16)
        - undated, 1 folder (Box 367, Folder 17)
    - Study Groups, 1955-1986; 5 boxes (1 partial)
      - Annual Report Materials, 1959-1981; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1961-1986; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - United States Foreign Trade Policy, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 2)
        - East-West Economic Relations, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 3)
        - Reappraisal of American Foreign Aid, 1969; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 4)
        - American Aid Policy in the Seventies, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 5)
        - German Democratic Republic and Germany's Future, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 6)
        - International Financial Problems, 1970; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 7)
        - International Financial Problems Proposal, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 8)
        - International Production, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 9)
        - Canadian-American Relations, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 10)
        - Foreign Economic Policy, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 11)
        - International Civil Aviation Policy, 1975; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 1)
        - Transnational Enterprises and International Relations, 1975-1977; 2 folders
          - Program for, 1976-1977; 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence and Background Paper, 1976; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 3)
        - United States Food and Agriculture Policy, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 4)
        - International Cooperation in Meeting Basic Human Needs, 1977; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 5)
        - Canada, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 6)
        - United States-Soviet Economic Relations, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 1)
        - United States Policy on International Information Flows, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 2)
        - Banking, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 3)
        - Problem of Extraterritoriality, 1982; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 4)
        - United States-Canada Trade Negotiation, 1986; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 5)
      - "Conceptual Approach", 1969-1972; portions of 2 boxes
        - 1969, 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 6)
        - 1970, 2 folders (Box 370, Folder 7 to 8)
        - 1970, 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 1)
        - 1971, 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 2)
        - 1972, 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 3)
      - Committee on Studies, 1955-1975; 2 folders (Box 371, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Current Issue Review Group, 1973-1976; 2 folders
        - International Trade, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 6)
        - International Transfer of Technology, 1976; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 7)
      - War and Peace Studies, 1974; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1983; 2 folders
        - 1965-1983, 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 1)
        - 1977-1983, 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - 1980s Project, 4 boxes (2 partial)
      - Correspondence and Memos, 1971-1980; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 3)
        - Coordinating Group, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 4)
        - Camps, Miriam, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 5)
        - Papers, 1974-1980; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 6)
        - Project Subjects and Groups, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 1)
      - Subject Files, 1952-1981; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - Bilderberg Conference, 1978; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 2)
        - Communist Countries and the World Economy, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 373, Folder 3 to 4)
        - Finances, Correspondence, 1976-1981; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 5)
        - Future of the Multinational Corporation, Survey, 1975-1976; 3 folders (Box 374, Folder 1 to 3)
        - Industrial Policy Materials, 1952-1981; portions of 2 boxes
          - 1952-1973, 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 4)
          - 1974-1977, 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 5)
          - 1978-1981, 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 6)
          - Article, circa 1980; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 1)
          - International Raw Materials Industry Information, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 2)
          - Letters of Acknowledgement, 1980; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 3)
          - Notes, 1978-1980; undated; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 4)
        - Mandates, 1975; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 5)
        - Paper Log, 1975; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 6)
        - Political Economy of North-South Relations, 1976; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 7)
        - Working Groups, Rapporteur's Summaries, 1976; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 8)
    - Writings and Lectures, 1940-1999; 11 boxes (1 partial)
      - Articles, 1953-1978; portions of 2 boxes
        - American Committee on United Europe, 1953; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 9)
        - American Political Science Association, 1959; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 10)
        - Britannica, 1957-1961; 2 folders (Box 375, Folder 11 to 12)
        - Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1973; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 1)
        - Challenge, 1960; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 2)
        - Collier's Encyclopedia, 1960; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 3)
        - Columbia Journal of World Business, 1965; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 4)
        - Current History, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 5)
        - English-Speaking Union, 1958; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 6)
        - Europa Archiv, 1957; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 7)
        - European Community Bulletin, 1955; 1959; 2 folders (Box 376, Folder 8 to 9)
        - European Yearbook, 1963; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 10)
        - German-American Trade News, 1973; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 11)
        - International Journal, 1963; 1974; 1978; 3 folders (Box 376, Folder 12 to 14)
        - International Organization, 1960; 1962; 2 folders (Box 376, Folder 15 to 16)
        - Round Table, 1967; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 17)
        - Princeton International Finance Section, 1953; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 18)
      - Books, 1947-1985; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - American Economic Policy Toward the Soviet Union: The Future in Perspective, Revised Final Draft, 1981; portions of 2 boxes
          - Chapters 1-2, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 19)
          - Chapter 3, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 20)
          - Chapter 4, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 21)
          - Chapter 5, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 1)
          - Chapter 6, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 2)
          - Chapter 7, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 3)
          - Chapter 8, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 4)
          - Chapter 9, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 5)
          - Chapter 10, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 6)
        - Dollars, Jobs, Trade, and Aid, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 7)
        - Industrial Policy for the United States?, 1980-1985; 3 folders (Box 377, Folder 8 to 10)
        - Past and Future Industrial Policy in the United States, 1980; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 11)
        - The Schuman Plan, 1947-1963; portions of 2 boxes
          - 1947-1959, 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 12)
          - 1953-1963, 5 folders (Box 378, Folder 1 to 5)
        - Second Industrial Revolution, 1960-1966; 2 folders (Box 378, Folder 6 to 7)
        - United States Economic Policy Toward the Communist World, 1968-1975; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 8)
      - Book Reviews, 1953-1999; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1953-1974; 2 folders (Box 378, Folder 9 to 10)
        - American Economic Review, 1953-1963; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1999; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 1)
        - Political Science Quarterly, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 2)
      - Council Publications, 1953-1992; 2 boxes (1 partial)
        - Anatomie Einer Elite (Book Report), 1979; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 3)
        - Aubrey, Henry (Trans-Atlantic Economic Cooperation), 1959-1967; 2 folders (Box 379, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Council on Foreign Relations Archives Introductory Essay, 1991; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 6)
        - Floating Exchange Rates, Stanley Black, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 7)
        - Foreign Affairs Fifty-Year Bibliography, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 8)
        - The New Multilateralism, 1981-1983; 4 folders
          - Correspondence and Reviews, 1983; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 9)
          - Early Drafts, Outlines, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 10)
          - Manuscript, 1983; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 11)
          - Review Meetings, 1983; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 12)
        - Oil Strategy and Politics, Levy, Walter, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 1)
        - Policy Book Program, 1962-1986; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 2)
        - Political Handbook and Atlas of the World, 1966-1972; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 3)
        - Richardson, Richard (Role of World Bank in Private Sector Development), 1992; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 4)
        - United States in World Affairs, 1953-1973; 2 folders (Box 380, Folder 5 to 6)
        - United States Trade Policy after the Kennedy Round, Evans, John, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous, 1958-1982; 2 folders (Box 380, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Lectures, 1955-1985; 15 folders
        - Bissell Professor Lecture, University of Toronto, 1979; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 1)
        - Columbia University Lectures, 1978; 1980; 1983; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 2)
        - Common Market, 1959-1970; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 3)
        - European Integration and Cooperation, 1962-1971; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 4)
        - Metropolitan Economic Association, 1955; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 5)
        - Radio and Television Talks, 1963-1972; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 6)
        - United States and European Integration, 1963-1974; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 7)
        - United States Foreign Trade and Foreign Trade Policy, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 8)
        - United States in the World Economy: A Fifty-Year View, 1983; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970-1985; 6 folders
          - 1970-1975, 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 10)
          - 1980, 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 11)
          - 1981, 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 12)
          - 1983, 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 13)
          - 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 14)
          - undated, 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 15)
      - Papers, 1940-1999; 4 boxes (1 partial)
        - 1940-1949, 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 1)
        - 1950-1959, 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 2)
        - 1960-1969, 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 3)
        - 1970-1972, 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 4)
        - 1973-1974, 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 5)
        - 1975, 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 6)
        - 1976-1977, 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 7)
        - 1978-1979, 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 1)
        - 1980, 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 2)
        - 1981-1982, 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 3)
        - 1983, 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 4)
        - 1984, 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 5)
        - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 1)
        - 1988-1989, 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 2)
        - 1990-1999, 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 3)
        - undated, 2 folders (Box 384, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1940-1999; 5 folders
          - 1940-1944, 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 1)
          - 1967-1981, 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 2)
          - 1976-1999, 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 3)
          - 1983-1985, 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 4)
          - 1989-1994, 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Notebooks, 1954; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 6)
    - Conferences, 1950-1999; 4 boxes
      - Council on Foreign Relations, 1964-1979; 9 folders
        - Corporation Service Seminars, 1964-1979; 3 folders
          - 1964-1966, 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 1)
          - 1972, 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 2)
          - 1979, 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 3)
        - Planning Conference, 1968 October 23-25; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 4)
        - Staff Conference, 1970 September 24-25; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 5)
        - East-West Trade Conference, 1973 November 3; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 6)
        - Polish-American Roundtable Conference, 1974 May 20-24; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 7)
        - International Commodity Buffer Stocks Conference, 1976 March 20; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 9)
      - Other Organizations, 1950-1999; 3 boxes
        - Acheson Conference, Johns Hopkins Foreign Policy Institute, 1984 April; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 1)
        - American-German Conference, 1964 November 12-15; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 2)
        - Canadian Institute of International Affairs Conference, 1978 June 8-10; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 3)
        - Columbia University Bicentennial Conference, 1954; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 4)
        - Columbia University Conference, "New Perspectives in Understanding East Central Europe," 1971 December 3-5, 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 5)
        - Conference on Research Initiatives, 1958 November 13-15; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 6)
        - Ditchley Foundations Conference on International Economic Institutions, 1979 January 12-14; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 7)
        - Elihu Root Lectures, 1963-1968; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 8)
        - European University Institute Conference, "National and International Economic Reconstruction in Western Europe", 1980-1999; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 9)
        - Institute for United States-Japan Relations, San Francisco State University, 1981 September 29; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 10)
        - International Trade Conference, Northern Illinois University College of Law, 1967-1994; 2 folders (Box 387, Folder 11 to 12)
        - Kennedy and Europe Conference, 1992 October; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 13)
        - Leffingwell Lectures, 1980; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 14)
        - Library of Congress Conference on Eastern Europe, 1980; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 1)
        - National Planning Association, 1979 December 11-1980 March 29; 2 folders
          - 1979 December 11, 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 2)
          - 1980 March 28-29, 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 3)
        - New York City Council on Economic Education, "Urban Civilization and World Trade", 1974 April 17; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 4)
        - Nobel Institute Conference on Western Democracies and World Problems, 1955; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 5)
        - North American Political Economy, Americas Society, 1986 February 27-28; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 6)
        - Political Science Association Meeting, 1959 September; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 7)
        - Private Planning Association of Canada, Canadian-American Committee Conference, 1960-1964; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 8)
        - Royal Institute of International Affairs Conference, "Italy and Her Partners," 1974 November 4-5, 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 9)
        - Schaetzel Luncheon Group, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 10)
        - School of Advanced International Studies, Johns Hopkins University, Conference on Africa, 1955; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 11)
        - Shimoda Conference, 1977; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 12)
        - Student Conference, United States Army, 1950-1960; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 13)
        - Subsidies Conference, 1977 January 14-15; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 14)
        - Trade Policy in the Eighties Conference, 1982; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 1)
        - United Nations Association of the United States of America, 1975-1979; more than 3 folders
          - International Division of Labor, 1975; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 2)
          - Moscow, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 3)
          - Moscow, Economics Panel, 1978 December 8-12; 2 folders (Box 389, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 1925-1998; 7 boxes (1 partial)
      - Canada, 1957-1991; 11 folders
        - Atlantic Council, 1980; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 1)
        - Canada Project, Author's Meeting, 1981; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 2)
        - Canada Talks, 1983; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 3)
        - Canada-United States Free Trade Agreement, 1990; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 4)
        - Canadian-American Relations Project, 1981 October; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 5)
        - Comments on Canada-United States-Japan Issues, 1985-1991; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 6)
        - United States-Canada Raw Materials, 1977; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 7)
        - Writings on Canada and Canadian-American Relations, 1965; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous, 1957-1987; 3 folders
          - 1957, 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 9)
          - 1984-1987, 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 10)
          - 1985-1986, 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 11)
      - Comments on Manuscripts and Articles, 1957-1982; 2 boxes (1 partial)
        - 1957-1960, 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 1)
        - 1961-1964, 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 2)
        - 1965-1968, 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 3)
        - 1969-1971, 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 4)
        - 1972-1974, 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 5)
        - 1975, 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 6)
        - 1976, 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 7)
        - 1976-1982, 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 1)
        - 1978, 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 2)
      - Committee for Economic Development, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, 1945-1995; portions of 2 boxes
        - Advisory Panel on the Non-Attribution Rule, 1976; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 4)
        - Diebold Biography, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 5)
        - East-West Trade, 1967; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 6)
        - Fellows, 1965-1978; more than 7 folders
          - Campbell, John C, 1971-1978; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 7)
          - Lowenthal, Abraham, 1974; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 8)
          - Manning, Bayless, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 9)
          - Miller, Francis Pickens, 1978; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 10)
          - Mosley, Philip, 1972; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 11)
          - Warneke, Steven, 1975; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 12)
          - Senior Council, Economists, 1965-1975; 4 folders (Box 392, Folder 13 to 16)
        - Foreign Economic Policy Task Force, 1960; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 17)
        - Gömöri, Endre, Meeting, 1982; 1 folder (Box 392, Folder 18)
        - Library Committee, 1978-1979; 2 folders
          - Memos, 1978; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 1)
          - Report, 1979; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 2)
        - Memos and Reports, 1969-1983; more than 2 folders
          - 1969, 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 3)
          - 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 393, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Nominations and Membership, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 6)
        - Trilateral Commission, 1975-1979; more than 4 folders
          - Canada, 1978; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 7)
          - Task Force on Access to Supplies, 1975; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 8)
          - Task Force on International Institutions, 1975; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 9)
          - Miscellaneous, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 393, Folder 10 to 11)
        - Miscellaneous, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 12)
      - European Coal and Steel Community, 1957; 1 folder (Box 393, Folder 13)
      - Foreign Economic Policy, 1946-1959; 1 folder (Box 394, Folder 1)
      - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade History, 1942-1988; 1 folder (Box 394, Folder 2)
      - Germany, Postwar, 1925-1972; more than 3 folders
        - Pamphlets, 1947-1950; 2 folders (Box 394, Folder 3 to 4)
        - Ruhr, 1925-1947; 1 folder (Box 394, Folder 5)
        - Ruhr, 1949-1972; 2 folders (Box 394, Folder 6 to 7)
      - International Trade Issues, 1971-1985; 1 folder (Box 394, Folder 8)
      - Internationalization of Bank, Study, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 394, Folder 9)
      - Lyndhurst Council, Historic Preservation, 1978-1984; 1 folder (Box 394, Folder 10)
      - Roberts, Priscilla, 1982-1998; 3 folders (Box 395, Folder 1 to 3)
      - Santoro, Carlo, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 395, Folder 4)
      - Senior Research Fellow Position, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 395, Folder 5)
      - Services Policy Advisory Committee, Office of the United States Trade Representative, 1983-1985; 1 folder (Box 395, Folder 6)
      - Technology Assessment, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 395, Folder 7)
      - Textile Negotiations, 1961; 1 folder (Box 395, Folder 8)
      - Trips, 1959-1979; portions of 2 boxes
        - Africa, 1959; 3 folders (Box 395, Folder 9 to 11)
        - Belgium, France, Switzerland, England, Germany, 1962; 1 folder (Box 395, Folder 12)
        - Japan, 1969; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 1)
        - Italy, Switzerland, England, 1973; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 2)
        - Soviet Union, England, 1974; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 3)
        - East Berlin, Vienna, Geneva, Brussels, 1975; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 4)
        - Soviet Union, 1977; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 5)
        - Paris, Bonn, Brussels, London, 1977; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 6)
        - Switzerland, Paris, Italy, 1978; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 7)
        - Paris, Berlin, London, 1979; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous Europe, 1964-1976; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 9)
      - World Peace Foundation, 1973-1976; 2 folders (Box 396, Folder 10 to 11)
  - Campbell, John, 1947-1986; 4 boxes (1 partial)
    - Books, 1967-1975; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1972; portions of 2 boxes
      - Alphabetical, 1959-1964; 4 folders
        - A, 1959-1963; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 13)
        - J, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 14)
        - P, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 15)
        - S, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1972; portions of 2 boxes
        - 1947-1961, 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 17)
        - 1955-1969, 1 folder (Box 396, Folder 18)
        - 1959-1963, 1 folder (Box 397, Folder 1)
        - 1959-1972, 1 folder (Box 397, Folder 2)
        - 1964-1966, 1 folder (Box 397, Folder 3)
        - 1964-1967, 2 folders (Box 397, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Evans, John, Correspondence, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 397, Folder 6)